Principles for Success. An ultra-mini-series adventure in 30
成功の原則。30分で楽しめる超短編アドベンチャー。
minutes and in 8 episodes.
8エピソードに分かれています。
Episode 1. The Call to Adventure.
エピソード1。冒険への誘い。
Before we begin, let me just establish the fact that I don't know much
始める前に、私はあまり知識がないことを明らかにします。
relative to what I need to know.
必要な知識に比べて。
Whatever success I've had in life has more to do with my
これまでの成功は、私が何を知っているかよりも、自分の無知にどう向き合うかに関係しています。
knowing how to deal with my not knowing than anything I know.
自分の無知にどう対処するかを知っていることが、私が知っている何よりも重要です。
That I should be telling other people what to do sounds kind
他の人に何をすべきかを指示するべきだということは、自分には少し矜恃を感じさせます。
of presumptuous to me.
私にとってちょっとおごり高ぶっているように感じます。
But I'm going to do it because I believe that the principles that
しかし、私はそれをするつもりです。なぜなら、私は成功してきた原則が他の人々が自分の目標を達成するのに役立つと信じているからです。
have made me successful could help others achieve their own goals.
私に成功をもたらしたものが他の人々が自分の目標を達成するのを助ける可能性があるからです。
I'm now at a stage in my own life in which it is much more important
私は自分自身の人生の段階にいます。それは、成功する方法について学んだことを伝えることが、自分自身の成功を追求するよりもずっと重要だと感じるようになりました。
to me to pass along what I've learned about how to be successful than
成功するための方法について学んだことを伝えることが、私には自分自身の成功を追求するよりも重要です。
to seek more success for myself.
自分自身の成功をさらに追求するよりも。
What you choose to do with these principles is up to you.
これらの原則をどう活用するかはあなた次第です。
You have to be an independent thinker because only you can develop your own
あなたは独自の考えを持たなければなりません。なぜなら、あなただけが自分自身の原則を自分の価値観に基づいて作り上げることができるからです。
principles based on your own values.
あなた自身の価値観に基づいた原則を持つ必要があります。
This brings me to my first and most fundamental principle which
これは私を最初で最も基本的な原則に導くものです
is that you need to think for yourself about what is true.
それは、真実について自分で考える必要があるということです。
So let's get started.
さあ、始めましょう。
Early on I discovered I needed principles.
最初から、私は原則が必要だと気付きました。
Principles are smart ways for handling things that happen over and over
原則は、何度も起こることをうまく処理する賢い方法です。
again in similar situations.
似たような状況で再び発生します。
There are principles for everything from skiing to parenting to
スキーから育児、料理などのすべてに原則があります。
cooking and so on.
料理など。
I'm going to share some of my most important overarching life
私は私の最も重要な全体的な人生のいくつかを共有しようと思っています。
principles that influence how we approach everything that we do.
私たちが何をするかに影響する原則。
I didn't start out with principles.
原則から始めたわけではありませんでした。
I acquired them over a lifetime of experiences.
長い経験の人生の中でそれらを獲得しました。
Mostly from making mistakes and reflecting on them.
主に間違いを犯し、それを考え返すことから。
My life principles are simple but they're not complete.
私の人生の原則はシンプルですが、完全ではありません。
I still struggle to make the best decisions and I still make mistakes and
最善の決定をするのにまだ苦労しており、また間違いを犯し続けています。
learn new principles all the time.
常に新しい原則を学んでいます。
This is the reality.
これが現実です。
At the beginning I needed to escape the conventions that surrounded me which
最初に、私は周りを取り巻く慣習から逃れる必要がありました。
meant that I needed to think for myself.
それは自分で考える必要があるということでした。
Unless you want to have a life that is directed by others you need to
他人によって導かれる人生を望まない限り、自分で何をするかを決める必要があります。
decide for yourself what to do.
自分自身が何をするかを決める必要があります。
And you need to have the courage to do it.
そして、それをする勇気が必要です。
But I didn't know that at first.
しかし、最初はそれを知りませんでした。
I only learned that from going on my adventure.
私はただ冒険に出ることでそれを学びました。
Looking back on my own journey I now see that time is like a river that carries
自分自身の旅を振り返ると、時間は私たちを運ぶ川のようであると気づく
us forward into encounters with reality that require us to make decisions.
私たちを現実との出会いに前進させ、私たちに決定を下させる
We can't stop our movement down this river and we can't avoid the encounters.
この川を下る動きを止めることも、出会いを避けることもできない
We can only approach them in the best possible way.
最善の方法でそれらに対処できるだけだ
In your lifetime you will face millions of decisions.
あなたの一生の中で、何百万もの決定に立ち向かうだろう
The quality of your decisions will determine the quality of your life.
あなたの決定の質が、あなたの人生の質を決定する
Over the course of my lifetime the most valuable things I've learned were
私の一生を通じて最も価値のあるものは、
the results of mistakes I reflected on to help form principles so I
反省して原則を形成するのに役立った過ちの結果は、
wouldn't make the same mistakes again.
同じ過ちを再び犯さないようにしたことである
These principles took me from being a very ordinary middle class kid from
これらの原則は私を非常に普通の中流階級の子供から連れて行きました
Long Island to becoming very successful as judged by conventional measures.
ロングアイランドから、従来の基準で非常に成功した人になるまで
They also gave me the meaningful work and meaningful relationships
それらは私に意義深い仕事と意義深い関係を与えてくれた
that I value even more than these conventional successes.
私がこれらの従来の成功よりもさらに大切にしているものです
People often ask me how I did it.
人々はしばしば私にどうやってそれをしたのか尋ねます
I can assure you it wasn't because of my uniqueness as a person.
私は保証します、それは私の個性に起因するものではありませんでした
It was the result of a unique approach to life I believe
私が信じる独自の人生へのアプローチの結果でした
almost anybody can adopt.
ほとんど誰でも取り入れることができるでしょう
It starts with embracing reality and dealing with it.
現実を受け入れ、対処することから始まります。
In episode two I'll explain what that means.
エピソード2では、それが何を意味するか説明します。